

△ PROFILE

Hello,i'm 18 yers old web developer from uzbekistan from Tashkent. I learned javascript, and MERN in Samar Badriddinov's courses,I have experienced in the field of frontend as a website developer. I have been coding for couples of years in series of jobs



tigeruzb777@gmail.com

93 106-38-13



Uzbekistan, Tashkent



prmominov.netlify.app

MO'MINOV XIKMATILLA

WEB DEVELOPER



EXPERIENCES

Oct, 2021 - Present

Freelancer

FREELANCER AND ONLINE TEACHER

 I'm teaching about web programming and i have many students and i'm a freelancer

Aug, 2020 - Oct, 2020

FulFil education

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

 I worked at FulFil education about 3 months as a Frontend developer



EDUCATIONS

Dec, 2019 - Aug, 2021

MUIMI - SPECIALIZED BOARDING SCHOOL

Sep, 2021 - Dec, 2021

LEAP ENGLISH EDUCATION CENTER

Oct, 2021 - Present

Backend

COURSE OF PROFESSIONAL WEB DEVELOPER SAMAR BADRIDDINOV

• My Frontend teachers is also Samar.B



SKILLS

- Html 5
- Css3
- vanilla Js, es6,es7 ...
- Sass
- Animate css/js
- React
- Redux

- Communicate
- Creative
- Teamwork